A life misunderestimated.
W. is a drama, history film directed by Oliver Stone.
The story of the eventful life of George W.
Bush—his struggles and triumphs, how he found both his wife and his faith—and
the critical days leading up to his decision to invade Iraq.
George W. Bush, played by Josh Brolin.
Speechwriter #1, played by Colin Hanks.
Karl Rove, played by Toby Jones.
Paul Wolfowitz, played by Dennis Boutsikaris.
Colin Powell, played by Jeffrey Wright.
Condoleezza Rice, played by Thandiwe Newton.
is a 2008 American biographical comedy-drama film based on the life of George W.
Directed by Oliver Stone and written by Stanley
Weiser, it stars Josh Brolin as Bush.
The supporting cast includes Elizabeth Banks, James Cromwell, Ellen Burstyn,
Thandiwe Newton, Jeffrey Wright, Scott Glenn, and Richard Dreyfuss.
Filming began on May 12, 2008, in Louisiana, and the film was
released on October 17, 2008 by Lionsgate.
The film explores themes of usa president, the white
house, politics, biography, president.
The tone is emotional.